Guide to the New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council Photographs PHOTOS 097
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council Photographs
circa 1944-1999
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council
Ward, Peter
PHOTOS 097
15.5 Linear Feet in 15 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
The New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council was born in of Depression-era struggles to improve conditions for employees of New York City hotels, restaurants and private clubs. In April of 1938 the Council was formed as an umbrella group of five AFL-affiliated unions and given sole authority to bargain for those unions. Over the years many other independent unions and locals have affiliated with the Council. The Council took on the work of administering welfare funds and running training and community service programs for its affiliates as a group. This collection contains photographic prints, negatives, and photograph albums from the New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council. Images depict union officers, staff, and departments; union activities including sports, education, elections, and picket lines; and union members at work in hotels.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by the New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council in 1997 and 2007. The accession numbers associated with this collection are 1997.006, 1997.026, NPA.2000.039, NPA.2002.060, NPA.2003.011, NPA.2004.039, and NPA.2008.024.
Arrangement
This collection has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
Historical/Biographical Note
The New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council was born in of Depression-era struggles to improve conditions for employees of New York City hotels, restaurants and private clubs. Several unsuccessful strikes and the emergence of a powerful Hotel Association representing the employers, spurred this effort. In April of 1938 the Council was formed as an umbrella group of five AFL-affiliated unions and given sole authority to bargain for those unions. Over the years many other independent unions and locals have affiliated with the Council. The Council took on the work of administering welfare funds and running training and community service programs for its affiliates as a group.
In the early 1930s conditions for workers in New York hotel and restaurant industry were harsh. Hours were long, work was seasonal, benefits were non-existent and there was no minimum wage. To make matters worse, gangsterism, which had flourished in the years of Prohibition, was rife in the industry. The American Federation of Labor-affiliated Hotel and Restaurant Employees Union concentrated its efforts on restaurant workers to the detriment of unskilled and semi-skilled workers in hotels. The failure of a 1934 strike sparked by a walkout of kitchen and dining room workers at the Waldorf Astoria led to several mergers of small independent unions attempting to gain leverage in confrontations with the powerful Hotel Association, representing hotel owners. In 1937 a newly formed Hotel, Restaurant and Cafeteria Employees Organizing Committee, led by left-wing militants, Jay Rubin, Miguel Garriga and Michael Obermeier, ran a hugely successful organizing campaign that further raised expectations.
In February 1938 eleven locals merged to form Hotel and Restaurant Employees Local 6. Local 6 was given jurisdiction over all hotel employees except those who were already members of building trades unions. On April 26, 1938 five unions joined together to form the Hotel Trades Council: H.E.R.E., Local 6; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 3; Building Service Employees International Union, Local 32A; International Brotherhood of Operating Engineers, Locals 94 and 94A; and International Brotherhood of Firemen, Oilers and Maintenance Mechanics, Local 56. The Council's first victory, in March 1938, was an agreement by the Hotel Association all grievances of union members would be taken up with the HTC. In subsequent years many other unions or locals either merged into Local 6 or joined the Council individually. In terms of numbers, Local 6 was the largest group in the Council and the most active in its affairs.
Jay Rubin was elected as first president of the Council, a position which he held until his retirement in 1978. Born in Gradno, Poland in 1904, Rubin had worked as and upholsterer and a baker before becoming a union organizer. He served on the Executive Board of the New York Central Labor Council and the Executive Board of the New York Convention and Visitors Bureau. A champion of improved health care for workers, he was an officer of the Hospital Review and Planning Council of Southern New York, the New York State Advisory Board of Medicaid, and the Labor-Management Council of Health and Welfare Plans. Rubin died in New York City on August 12, 1990.
In January 1939 the Council concluded a comprehensive wages and hours agreement, with strong support from New Deal state and municipal authorities. Among its historic provisions were time-and-a-half pay for overtime, paid vacations, free uniforms, a curb on split shifts, dues checkoff, an anti-discrimination clause, no dismissal for union activity, and establishment of an arbitration procedure. While some hotels signed the agreement immediately, many others held out for years -- the last few signing in the 1950s.
In 1944 the HTC achieved an industry-wide, employer-financed and union-managed benefits program. A Hotel Joint Employment Agency was established under the 1949 contract -- a major remedy against seasonal fluctuations and discriminatory or arbitrary hiring practices; after a period of adjustment this no-fee agency was fully functioning by 1951, when 22,000 jobs were supplied to members. A Health Center, offering free basic medical care to hotel workers and their families, was opened in 1950. In 1966 the Hotel Trades Council established the Neighborhood Service Councils, which provided members with a wide range of services, from housing assistance to legal advice and medical referrals. It has also run a Hotel Industry Training Program, including a school for for young people seeking work in the industry and for workers interested in upgrading or changing their category of employment.
Over the years the Council expanded to include unionized painters, telephone operators, maintenance workers, upholsterers, clerical workers and others employed in hotels, restaurants and clubs. By the 1980s, when the Council was headed by Rubin's successor, Vito J. Pitta, the HTC represented 25,000 members affiliated with nine locals of eight international unions. While continuing to struggle against economic downturns, and anti-union or dishonest employers, especially in smaller enterprises throughout the City, the Council claims to offer, through its contracts, the best wages and benefits available to hotel workers anywhere in the world.
Related Archival Materials
New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council Records (WAG 123)
Scope and Content Note
This collection contains photographic prints, negatives, and photograph albums from the New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council. Around two-thirds of the photographs date from the 1940s through the mid-1980s. The negatives and round one-third of the photographs date from the mid-1980s through late-1990s. Images depict union officers, staff and departments; union activities including sports, education, elections, and picket lines; and union members at work in hotels.
Strikes and lockouts -- New York (State) -- New York.; Strikes and lockouts.; New York (N.Y.) |v Pictorial works.; New York (N.Y.) |x History |y 20th century |v Pictorial works.; Photographic prints.; Photographs.; Labor unions -- Officials and employees.; Labor unions |z New York (State) |z New York |v Pictorial works.; Negatives (photographic); New York (N.Y.); Demonstrations |v Pictorial works.; Demonstrations |z New York (State) |z New York |v Pictorial works.; Labor union members.; Labor unions |v Pictorial works.; Sports |v Pictorial works.; Picketing.; Picketing |v Pictorial works.; Color photographs.; New York Hotel Trades Council.; New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council; Ward, Peter
- Prints
  - Education
    - Business Agent Training Course (Box 1)
    - Scholarship Funds (Box 1)
    - ITP Education (Box 1)
    - ITP Graduation, 1991 (Box 1)
    - Scholarships, 1991 (Box 1)
    - East Harlem Music School (Box 1)
    - ITP Grad, 1989 (Box 1)
    - ITP Graduation, 1993 (Box 1)
    - ITP Graduation, 1989 (Box 1)
    - ITP Grad (Box 1)
    - Scholarships, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Scholarships, 1989 (Box 1)
    - ITP (Box 1)
    - Scholarships, 1993 (Box 1)
    - ITP Classes (Box 1)
    - Scholarship, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Scholarship And ITP Grad, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Hotel Olympics, 1990-1991 (Box 1)
    - Hotel Olympics, 1991 (Box 1)
    - Olympics, 1992 (Box 1)
    - CIH Mets Day (Box 1)
    - Leadership Training Course (Box 3)
    - General Education (Box 3)
    - General Education (Box 3)
    - Literacy Tests (Box 3)
    - Scholarship, 1989 (Box 3)
    - Scholarship, 1987 (Box 3)
    - Leadership Training Classes (Box 3)
    - Students (Box 3)
  - Sports
    - Chess (Box 2)
    - General Sports (Box 2)
    - Softball, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Softball, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Softball, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Bowling (Box 1)
    - Ping-Pong (Box 1)
    - Soccer (Box 1)
    - Swimming (Box 1)
    - Baseball (Box 1)
    - Basketball Awards, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Basketball (Box 1)
    - Basketball - 1986 (Box 1)
    - Softball (Box 2)
    - Basketball, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Softball, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Softball, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Basketball, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Basketball, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Basketball (Box 1)
    - Basketball - Sports (Box 1)
    - Baseball - Sports (Box 2)
  - Picket Lines
    - Miscellaneous Photos (Box 2)
    - Salmas - Picket Lines (Box 2)
    - NY Post (Box 2)
    - NYNEX (Box 2)
    - Local Supporters L829 (Box 2)
    - Hallocan House (Box 2)
    - WA (Box 2)
    - Hospital Strike - Spring And Summer '62 1959 (Box 2)
    - GE Strike (Box 2)
    - Macklowe (Box 2)
    - Elmhurst Manor (Box 2)
    - Princeton Club (Box 2)
    - Broadway Diner (Box 2)
    - Essex House (Box 2)
    - Philadelphia Teachers (Box 2)
    - TWA Strike - 5/86 (Box 2)
    - Eastern Airlines (Box 2)
    - Japanese Airline (Box 2)
    - NABET (Box 2)
    - CWA (Box 2)
    - Greyhound (Box 2)
    - Cass (Box 2)
    - Benkay (Box 2)
    - Daily News (Box 2)
    - Marriott Marquis (Box 2)
    - NY Hilton (Box 2)
    - Novotel (Box 2)
    - Marriott (Box 2)
    - Strike Vote - Contract Negotiations, 1995 (Box 2)
    - Marriott Laguardia (Box 3)
    - Essex Strikes 101 (Box 3)
    - Tavern On The Green (Box 3)
    - Marriott Marquis Boy Scout Rally (Box 3)
    - Roll Call (Box 3)
    - Regines (Box 3)
    - Boxtrees (Box 3)
    - Delmonicos (Box 3)
    - Staten Island Hotel (Box 3)
    - Plaza Picket (Box 2)
    - American Restaurant (Box 3)
    - Al - Mounia (Box 3)
    - Bronx Park Motel Strike (Box 3)
    - Drexel (Box 3)
    - Plaza Hotel (Box 2)
    - Drake (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous hanging folder (Box 3)
    - Las Vegas Strike (Box 3)
    - Rainbow (Box 3)
    - Grand Hyatt (Box 3)
    - Picket Lines / Rallies / Lobby Meetings (Box 3)
    - Harvard Cub sic Picket Lines, 1948 (Box 3)
    - SEIU Local 1199 (Box 3)
    - Westinghouse (Box 3)
    - Miami Strike - Picket Lines, 1955 (Box 3)
    - Hectors (Box 3)
    - Puerto Rico -Picket Lines, 1964 (Box 3)
    - Hospital Strike (Box 3)
    - Grand Hyatt Lobby Meeting (Box 3)
    - Retirement Shots (Box 4)
  - Members
    - A (Box 4)
    - B (Box 4)
    - C (Box 4)
    - D (Box 4)
    - E (Box 4)
    - F (Box 4)
    - G - Members (Box 4)
    - Golobrieski, Joe (Box 4)
    - Glassgold, Adolph C. (Box 4)
    - H (Box 4)
    - I (Box 4)
    - J (Box 4)
    - K (Box 4)
    - L (Box 4)
    - M (Box 5)
    - Ralph Mcgiel (Box 5)
    - N (Box 5)
    - O (Box 5)
    - P / Q (Box 5)
    - R (Box 5)
    - S (Box 5)
    - T (Box 5)
    - U - V - W - X - Y - Z (Box 5)
    - NP97 [NPA08-24] (Box 5)
    - Inquiring Photographers (Box 5)
    - Group Shots (Box 6)
  - Departments
    - Kitchen Department (Box 6)
    - Banquet Department (Box 6)
    - Statler - Upholstery (Box 6)
    - Uniforms (Box 6)
    - Front Service (Box 6)
    - Front Desk (Box 6)
    - Painters (Box 6)
    - Club Department (Box 6)
    - Room Attendants (Box 6)
    - Waiters And Waitresses (Box 6)
    - Laundry Department (Box 6)
    - Housekeeping Department (Box 6)
    - Floor Housekeepers (Box 6)
    - Bar Department (Box 6)
    - Electrical Workers (Box 6)
    - Bar (Box 6)
    - Maintenance (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous - Department (Box 6)
  - Organizations
    - CIH Hospital (Box 6)
    - Insurance (Box 7)
    - Joint Employment Committee (Box 7)
    - Unemployment Insurance (Box 7)
    - Unemployment Conference - Washington (Box 7)
    - UFMF Brooklyn (Box 7)
    - Joint Legislative Committee Hearings (Box 7)
    - Housing (Box 7)
    - Dr. Hennig, Geo, C. (Box 7)
    - Health And Health Legislation (Box 7)
    - Pensioners (Box 7)
    - Exposition (Box 7)
    - Employment Agency (Box 7)
    - Hotel Placement Office (Box 7)
    - Bayberry - Organization (Box 7)
    - Committees Organizations (Box 7)
    - Pensioners (Box 7)
    - Pensioners (Box 7)
    - Pensioners Lobby Meetings (Box 7)
    - Pensioners, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Charity Organizations (Box 7)
    - Optical Center (Box 7)
    - MHAP (Box 7)
    - Social Services Department Organizations (Box 7)
    - Queens Medical Center - Organizations, 1995 (Box 7)
    - Legal Aid (Box 7)
    - UFMF # 1 (Box 7)
    - Union Family Medical Fund (Box 7)
    - Medical, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Dental (Box 7)
    - Dental Organizations (Box 7)
    - New Med. Center (Box 7)
    - Pensioners Lunch, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Pensioners Lunch, 1983 (Box 7)
    - Pensioners Lunch, 1984 (Box 7)
    - Pensioners Party (Box 7)
    - Prepaid Legal (Box 8)
      - Union Officers / Staff (Box not specified)
        - Gertrude Lane (Box 8)
        - Gertrude Lane (Box 8)
        - H. Lawless (Box 8)
        - Emmanuel Lisanti (Box 8)
        - Lurie, Jerome (Box 8)
        - Lynch, Lon (Box 8)
        - Peter Michaud (Box 8)
        - Louise Matthews (Box 8)
        - Domenick Menick (Box 8)
        - John Morgan (Box 8)
        - M. Montalvo (Box 8)
        - Marie Marino (Box 8)
        - Ralph Mandrew (Box 8)
        - Charles Martin (Box 8)
        - Gladys Morris (Box 8)
        - Mann, Michael (Box 8)
        - Moreno, Marie (Box 8)
        - James Marley (Box 8)
        - George Meany includes an image with President Eisenhower speaking (Box 8)
        - Mahoney (Box 8)
        - Claude Mason (Box 8)
        - Edward S. Miller (Box 8)
        - Edward P. Mulrooney (Box 8)
        - D. Nadel (Box 8)
        - Mike Obermeier (Box 8)
        - Ottley, Peter B. (Box 8)
        - Alberta Porter (Box 8)
        - Louis Pavlista (Box 8)
        - Ernie Peters (Box 8)
        - Vincent Pitta (Box 8)
        - A. P. Randolph (Box 8)
        - Rinauldo, Angelo (Box 8)
        - Angelo Rinauldo (Box 8)
        - Reilly, Jack (Box 8)
        - Eva Rodriguez (Box 8)
        - Howard Rohr (Box 8)
        - David Sola (Box 8)
        - Walter Smith (Box 8)
        - Fred Spinner (Box 8)
        - Ernest Schneider (Box 8)
        - Spahn, William (Box 8)
        - Martin Segal (Box 8)
        - Sheerin (Box 8)
        - Serafin (Box 8)
        - Summers, Eddie (Box 8)
        - Cecil I. Smith (Box 8)
        - F. Schulz (Box 8)
        - Saulnier (Box 8)
        - Sandstrom, Lennart (Box 8)
        - Al Symanski (Box 8)
        - Peter Seitz (Box 8)
        - Richard Sirch (Box 8)
        - Betty Smith (Box 8)
        - Charlotte Stern (Box 8)
        - David Siegal (Box 8)
        - Aryel Santibanz (Box 8)
        - Carl Schutt (Box 8)
        - F. Schultz (Box 8)
        - Nick Suckman (Box 8)
        - Margaret Tannebaum (Box 8)
        - Jack Townsend (Box 8)
        - John Turchiano (Box 8)
        - Audrey Throne-Lunch (Box 8)
        - Harry Van Arsdale (Box 8)
        - Al Vollero (Box 8)
        - Matty Thompson (Box 8)
        - W. J. Trent Jr. (Box 8)
        - Vozoris (Box 8)
        - Milton Waitzman (Box 8)
        - Nettie Willie (Box 8)
        - George Wilson (Box 8)
        - Jack Weinberger (Box 8)
        - Tom Wilson (Box 8)
        - Betty Ziff (Box 8)
        - Weinberger, Jack (Box 9)
        - Wolfgang, Myra (Box 9)
        - Williams, Harold (Box 9)
        - International Union (Box 9)
        - International Brotherhood Of Electrical Workers (IBEW) (Box 9)
        - Editors (Box 9)
        - Local 6 Headquarters (Box 9)
        - Retirement: Marley, Jackson, Michaud (Box 9)
        - Retirement: Blair, Menick, Mautin (Box 9)
        - Group Shots (Box 9)
        - Group Shots (Box 9)
      - Elections (Box not specified)
      - Elections (Box 9)
      - Local 6 Election (Box 9)
      - Local Elections 6, 1988 (Box 9)
      - Elections (Box 9)
      - Poor People’s Campaign (Box 9)
      - Political Education Committee (Box 9)
      - Workmen’s Compensation (Box 9)
      - New York City (Box 9)
      - Albany Delegation - Hotel And Club Workers PEC (Box 9)
      - Puerto Rico And Pr Organs (Box 9)
      - Equal Opportunity (Box 9)
      - Anti-Apartheid Demo, May, 1986 (Box 9)
      - Awards (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous (Box not specified)
    - War Activity - Miscellaneous WWII - including Spanish Victory Committee, war bonds, etc. (Box 9)
    - War Activity - Miscellaneous WWII - including Spanish Victory Committee, war bonds, etc. (Box 10)
    - Scenery (Box 10)
    - Cerebral Palsy (Box 10)
    - Around The Home (Box 10)
    - Race Relations (Box 10)
    - Local 1422 (Box 10)
    - Zeckendorf, William (Box 10)
    - Local 1005 (Box 10)
    - Local 153 (Box 10)
    - Local 144 (Box 10)
    - Local 56 (Box 10)
    - Local 43 (Box 10)
    - Local 1 (Box 10)
    - Local 3 (Box 10)
    - Transport Workers Union (Box 10)
    - Other Unions (Box 10)
    - Trade Show (Box 10)
    - Lily Lawrence (Box 10)
    - United Way (Box 10)
    - Convention & Visitors (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous International Photos - International (Box 10)
    - International Convention Chicago - International (Box 10)
    - Conventions (Box 10)
    - Hearings (Box 10)
    - Haiti Aid (Box 10)
    - Grievances (Box 10)
    - Conventions (Box 10)
    - Hotel Association (Box 10)
    - Hospitalization Insurance (Box 10)
    - Farm Workers (Box 10)
    - Forums (Box 10)
    - Freedom Rally - Washington (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
    - “No Hotel Tax” Rally (Box 10)
    - Visitors And Conv. Bureau (Box 10)
    - Coal Miners (Box 10)
    - Housing (Box 10)
    - Hurricane Relief (Box 10)
    - Foreign Affairs (Box 10)
    - Smoking (Box 10)
    - Pix B. Jeith () (Box 11)
    - AFL-CIO = 1st Constitutional Convention (Box 11)
    - Caesar Chavez (Box 11)
    - Jesse Jackson (Box 11)
    - Political (Box 11)
    - Jerry Brown (Box 11)
    - Wagner, Mayor Robert F. (Box 11)
    - Javits, Jacob K. (Box 11)
    - Hotel Workers Committees - 17th and 18th C. D. (Box 11)
    - Legislative Union Activities (Box 11)
    - Greek Relief Fund (Box 11)
    - Bond Drives (Box 11)
    - Managers (Box 11)
    - Greater New York Fund (Box 11)
    - Local 153 (Box 11)
    - Boland, Msgr. John (Box 11)
  - Hotels
    - Hotels - History (Box 11)
    - Hotel Safety (Box 11)
    - Hotels (Box 11)
    - Hotel Execs. (Box 11)
    - Motels: Hotels$ (Box 11)
    - Edison Hotels (Box 11)
    - Astor (Box 12)
    - Alden (Box 12)
    - Algonquin (Box 12)
    - America (Box 12)
    - Ambassador (Box 12)
    - Beaux Arts (Box 12)
    - Bedford (Box 12)
    - Beckman (Box 12)
    - Biltmore (Box 12)
    - Beefsteak Charlie’s (Box 12)
    - Belmont Plaza (Box 12)
    - Bristol (Box 12)
    - Capitol (Box 12)
    - Carlton And Old Ritz (Box 12)
    - Carlyle (Box 12)
    - Chatham (Box 12)
    - Chelsea (Box 12)
    - Claridge (Box 12)
    - Cloud Club (Box 12)
    - Commodore (Box 12)
    - Cosmopolitan Club (Box 12)
    - Croydon (Box 12)
    - Hotel Fourteen (Box 12)
    - Dixie (Box 12)
    - Drake (Box 12)
    - Emerson (Box 12)
    - Essex House (Box 12)
    - Fifth Avenue (Box 12)
    - Forest Hill Inn (Box 12)
    - Gladstone (Box 12)
    - Gotham (Box 12)
    - Grand Central Hotels (Biltmore, Commodore, Roosevelt) (Box 12)
    - Governor Clinton (Box 12)
    - Granada (Box 12)
    - Gramercy Park (Box 12)
    - Grosvenor (Box 12)
    - Hampshire House (Box 12)
    - Henry Hudson (Box 12)
    - Holley (Box 12)
    - Holiday Inn (Box 12)
    - Howard Johnson Motor Lodge (Box 12)
    - Harbor View Club (Box 12)
    - Inn At 57th St (Box 12)
    - India Club (Box 12)
    - Kenmore Hall (Box 12)
    - Lucerne (Box 12)
    - Lafayette (Box 12)
    - Le Marquis (Box 12)
    - Lotus Club (Box 12)
    - Loew’s Hotel (Box 12)
    - Lexington (Box 12)
    - Lincoln (Box 12)
    - Lombardy (Box 12)
    - Marco Polo (Box 12)
    - Manhattan (Box 12)
    - Millenium (Box 12)
    - Marcy (Box 12)
    - Martinque (Box 12)
    - Mcalpin (Box 12)
    - New York Athletic Club (Box 12)
    - New Yorker (Box 12)
    - New Weston (Box 12)
    - Oliver Cromwell (Box 12)
    - Overseas Press Club (Box 12)
    - Olcott (Box 12)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 12)
    - Pennsylvania Mess (Box 12)
    - Picadilly (Box 12)
    - Pierre (Box 12)
    - Park Royal (Box 12)
    - Park Sheraton (Box 12)
    - Parkside (Box 13)
    - Park Crescent (Box 13)
    - Paris (Box 13)
    - Penta (Box 13)
    - Pinnacle Club (Box 13)
    - Palace (Box 13)
    - Plaza (Box 13)
    - Parker-Meridien (Box 13)
    - Prince George (Box 13)
    - Realty Hotels (Box 13)
    - Roosevelt (Box 13)
    - Russian Tea Room (Box 13)
    - Russell (Box 13)
    - St. George (Box 13)
    - St. Moritz (Box 13)
    - St. Regis (Box 13)
    - St. Regis (Box 13)
    - Savoy Hilton (Box 13)
    - Savoy-Plaza (Box 13)
    - Seymoure (Box 13)
    - Summit (Box 13)
    - Sheraton Towers (Box 13)
    - Sheraton Motor Inn (Box 13)
    - Sloane House (Box 13)
    - Stock Exchange (Box 13)
    - Sheraton East (Box 13)
    - Sheraton-Plaza (Box 13)
    - Sherry Netherlands (Box 13)
    - Sixtyeast Club (Box 13)
    - Stanhope (Box 13)
    - Statler (Box 13)
    - Taft (Box 13)
    - Ten Park Avenue (Box 13)
    - Theresa (Box 13)
    - Tuscanny (Sic) (Box 13)
    - Travelers (Box 13)
    - Traffic Club (Box 13)
    - Town House (Box 13)
    - Time S Square (Box 13)
    - Tudor (Box 13)
    - Uptown Club (Box 13)
    - Vanderbilt (Box 13)
    - Victoria (Box 13)
    - Vista (Box 13)
    - Waldorf Astoria Mess (Box 13)
    - Warwick (Box 13)
    - Walton (Box 13)
    - Winslow (Box 13)
    - Whitman (Box 13)
    - Weylin (Box 13)
    - Westbury (Box 13)
    - Wellington (Box 13)
    - Woodward (Box 13)
    - Woodstock (Box 13)
    - Winthrop (Box 13)
    - Windsor (Box 13)
    - Yale Club (Box 13)
    - Zeckendorf (Box 13)
    - Clubs (Box 13)
  - Addendum 1
    - Unnamed Color Group Shots - 1997 1996 (Box not specified)
    - Children’s Christmas Party (Box 15)
    - Contract Negotiations, 1995 (Box 15)
    - Delegates (Box 15)
    - Drake Hotel Strike (Box 15)
    - Demonstrations Miscellaneous 1996 (Box 15)
    - HTC Transition (Box 15)
    - Princess Alela (Box 15)
    - Basketball, 1996 (Box 15)
    - Bed Making Contest, 1996 (Box 15)
    - Blood Drive (Box 15)
    - Check Disbursements (Box 15)
    - Labor Day, 1996 (Box 15)
    - Florence Grogan (Box 15)
    - Local Interns 6 (Box 15)
    - Israel Bonds (Box 15)
    - ITP Graduation, 1996 (Box 15)
    - Kid’s Day, 1996 (Box 15)
    - Pensioners (Box 15)
    - Ernie Peters (Box 15)
    - Pharmacy (Box 15)
    - Political (Box 15)
    - Local Installation 6 (Box 15)